# 前几天手贱给自己家的洗衣机
A few days ago my hands were out of control
# 加了几个轱辘
to attach a few wheels to my washing machine
# 让它能够自由的活动
to let it move freely
# 它却一不小心绊了一跤
but it tripped up
# 摔坏了
and it was broken
# 家人说这一切都是我的错
my family blamed all of these on me
# 拒绝给我买新的洗衣机
they refused to buy me a new one
# 而且以后的衣服都让我来洗
I became the "washing machine" of the family ever since
# 但是说自己用双手洗衣服特别累
But it is tiring if I use bare hands to wash clothes
# 所以说我准备做一个自动洗衣服的机器人
therefore I want to make a robot that automatically does the job
# 随后，再加上我这个大铁搓衣板
Finally, after adding this huge iron washboard to the system,
# 这个洗衣机器人就算是完成了
the washing robot is born
# 下面我为大家介绍一下
let me introduce to you
# 这个洗衣机怎么使用
how to wash with the robot
# 下面我们把这个巨型的铁搓衣板插入这个机器人中
First, let's insert the iron washboard to the robot
# 啊像这样
like this
# 然后调整好姿势
then, adjust its pose
# 姿势调整完之后
after that,
# 我们把机器人里面的起更跟手臂链接
let's pull this rod out and connect it to its hands
# 啊，像这样，拧上一点
like this. tighten it a little bit
# 然后把衣服放到机器人手臂的下方
then, put the clothes under the hands of the robot
# 打开开关
turn the switch on
# 它就会模仿人类这样洗衣服
it will start mimicking a human washing the clothes
# 这样洗出来的衣服比较有灵魂
the clothes washed in this way seem more spiritual
# 穿上比较舒服也比较干净
they're more comfortable and cleaner
# 可能有人会说这样洗衣服会比较慢
people may say that the robot works very slowly
# 我们还可以调快加它个速度
we can accelerate its speed
# 像这样
like this
# 这样它就会快速地给我们洗衣服
it will wash the clothes at a higher pace
# 洗的时间比较长了之后
after a while,
# 衣服表面会比较干
the surface of the clothes will be relatively dry
# 我们只需要插上水泵
we just need to plug in the water pump
# 从它的眼睛里就会喷出水了 会湿润我们的衣服
the robot will start spraying water from its eyes to moisturize our clothes
# 这样洗出来的衣服会比较好
the clothes will be washed better in this way
# 当我们洗完一件衣服之后
after we've finished with one piece of clothing
# 我们还可以换另一件
we can change another one
# 洗完这件衣服之后
after it finishes washing the entire clothes
# 可以放下一件
let's change another one
# 下一件放这
leave this here
# 然后再打开开关重新洗
turn the switch on and wash it again
# 有了这个洗衣机器人之后
With this washing robot
# 我们人就不会这么累
we humans won't be very tired anymore
# 可以在它旁边一边喝着茶
you can have a cup of tea
# 一边看它洗衣服
while watching it wash
# 非常地惬意
very relaxing